George Sandoval

Oakland, CA 94610 gssandoval09@gmail.com (914) 256-7733

A friendly, outgoing, and charismatic individual aiming to excel in any work environment. I enjoy arts & crafts, being creative, working together with others or alone to get the job done. Eager to gain experience and grow, fast learner, 5 + years in customer service experience. Fluent in both English and Spanish.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Lyft Driver

Lyft - Oakland, CA

November 2018 to Present

- Ensured that customer arrived safely and timely to their destination while ensuring the customer was comfortable and happy each ride.
- Maintained my vehicle clean and always stocked with water and hand sanitizer for customer use.
- Maintained my 5 star rating from customer satisfaction feedback.
- Managed routes through use of iPhone app technology.

Kitchen Supervisor

Pinterest - San Francisco, CA February 2018 to Present

- Perform all Kitchen duties as well as additional supervisory duties listed below.
- Maintain a clean and safe working environment according to Health Department regulations.
- Assist with key human resource functions by enforcing all store/department policies, minimizing overtime, training new employees, monitoring staff breaks, and completing documentation in a timely manner (i.e. one on one meetings, feedback for performance evaluations, disciplinary actions, and terminations).
- Supervise duties of Kitchen staff, including minimizing overtime, monitoring staff breaks and keeping staff productive during slow periods.
- Assist Kitchen Manager in department development and training.
- Monitor credits, spoilage and shrink through effective organization, rotation and follow through.
- Ensure all products meet quality standards through proper labeling, rotation, cleanliness, sanitation, and hygiene, and by only selling fresh product.

Valet Parking

Penninsula parking - San Francisco, CA December 2017 to January 2019

- Assisted guests with opening/closing vehicle doors.
- Tagged guest vehicle keys with date & time, registration number, make/model, room number or contact number of the guest.
- Provided correct counter token or receipt of valet parking to the guest.

- Verified guests token or receipt with the one attached to the key before handing over keys or vehicle to the guest.
- Effectively parked and retrieved guests cars without causing damage to the vehicle.
- Drove and operated manual and automatic transmission vehicles.
- Provided guests with direction and local areas of interest and activities.
- Ensured vehicles are legally parked and to maintain a smooth and efficient flow of traffic.
- Ensured all guest's valet experiences were memorable, unique and as per company's standards.
- Maintained the security of vehicles, belongings kept inside the car and vehicle keys.
- Documented and reported all vehicle incidents like damages, accidents, theft, missing articles etc.
- Reported accidents, injuries, and unsafe work conditions to the supervisor or manager.
- Re-routed traffic when parking facility reaches maximum capacity and ensure staff is informed.

Housekeeping

Fairy - San Francisco, CA February 2018 to November 2018

- Performed a variety of cleaning activities such as sweeping, mopping, dusting and polishing
- Ensured all rooms are cared for and inspected according to standards
- Protected equipment and made sure there were no inadequacies
- Worked with cleaning chemicals responsibly and wore appropriate job attire.
- Followed written tasks per household and completed all on time.

Dishwasher/Prep Cook

Outback Steakhouse - Irving, TX September 2017 to January 2018

- Cleaned tableware, washed dishes, glassware, flatware, pots, or pans, using dishwashers or by hand.
- Maintained kitchen work areas, equipment, or utensils in clean and orderly condition.
- Stored supplies or goods in kitchens or storage areas.
- Sorted and removed trash, placing it in designated pickup areas.
- Stocked supplies, such as food or utensils, in serving stations, cupboards, refrigerators, or salad bars.
- Cleaned and prepared various foods for cooking or serving. Prepared foods for cooking or serving.
- Cleaned food preparation areas, facilities, or equipment.
- Loaded and unload trucks that deliver or pick up food or supplies, moved equipment, supplies or food to required locations.
- Arranged tables and dining areas.

Food Service Worker Northern Westchester Hospital

Northwell Health - Mount Kisco, NY February 2015 to July 2017

- Assisted in preparing dishes for patients in accordance to doctors' instructions for each individual patient
- Placed trays in pushcarts and physically pushed them throughout hospital corridors to assigned floors.
- Collected food trays and dirty dishes and carted them back to the kitchen for washing.
- Maintained kitchen including trash disposal, sweeping, mopping, and washing and drying dishware, glassware and flatware.
- Restocked refrigerators, freezers & dry goods on room service line.

- Expanded interpersonal and professional communication skills through serving customers, working with peers, and following the directions of supervisors and managers.

Sales Associate

Party City - Mount Kisco, NY August 2013 to June 2014

- Answered customer inquiries regarding Party City goods and services, used selling techniques to recommend products.
- Assembled product displays, organized stockroom inventory.
- maintained store cleanliness, such as sweeping, emptying garbage bins and cleaned counter tops.
- Performed cashier duties as needed.
- Answered customer phones calls.
- Unlocked store at start of shifts and lock up for security purposes

Education

Westchester Community College - Valhalla, NY September 2014 to June 2017

Fox Lane High School - Mount Kisco, NY September 2010 to June 2014

Graphic design

Academy of Art University - San Francisco, CA February 2018

Skills

CUSTOMER SERVICE (5 years), RETAIL SALES (1 year), MICROSOFT OFFICE (10+ years), Food Service (4 years)

Certifications/Licenses

driver's license

Additional Information

Proficient in Microsoft office, food handling, customer service, fluent in both English and Spanish, time management, adaptability, creativity, self-confidence, collaboration.